<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.sourceforge.liferea.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
  <name>Liferea</name>
  <summary>RSS feed reader</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">RSS Feedreader</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Lecteur de flux RSS</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Liferea is an abbreviation for Linux Feed Reader. It is a news aggregator for online news feeds. It supports a number of different feed formats including RSS/RDF, CDF and Atom. There are many other news readers available, but these others are not available for Linux or require many extra libraries to be installed. Liferea tries to fill this gap by creating a fast, easy to use, easy to install news aggregator for GTK/GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">لايفريا هو مجمّع أخبار لتلقيمات الأخبار. يدعم عددًا من أنساق التلقيمات مثل RSS/RDF و CDF و Atom. يوجد العديد من قارئات تلقيمات الأخبار لكنها إما غير متوفرة على لينكس أو تتطلب الكثير من المكتبات الإضافية. يحاول لايفريا سد هذه الهوّة بتوفير مجمّع أخبار سهل الاستخدام و التثبيت لجنوم.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Liferea ist eine Abkürzung für »Linux Feed Reader«. Es ist ein Aggregator für Online-News-Feeds. Es unterstützt eine Reihe von verschiedenen Feed-Formaten, wie RSS/RDF, CDF und Atom. Es gibt viele andere Aggregatoren, doch diese sind nicht für Linux verfügbar oder setzen voraus dass viele externe Bibliotheken installiert sind. Liferea versucht diese Lücke zu schließen indem ein schneller, leicht zu benutzender, und leicht zu installierender Nachrichten-Aggregator für GTK/Gnome erstellt wird.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Liferea es una abreviatura de «Linux Feed Reader». Es un agregador de canales de noticias en línea. Es compatible con varios formatos de canales, como RSS/RDF, CDF y Atom. Existen otros lectores de noticias, pero o no están disponibles en Linux o necesitan de muchas bibliotecas adicionales para funcionar. Liferea trata de llenar ese vacío con un agregador rápido y fácil de usar y de instalar para GTK/GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Liferea est l’abréviation de Linux Feed Reader. C’est un agrégateur de flux pour sites web. Il gère un certain nombre de formats de flux dont RSS/RDF, CDF et ATOM. D’autres lecteurs de flux existent mais soit ils ne sont pas disponibles pour Linux, soit ils nécessitent beaucoup de bibliothèques externes pour être installés. Liferea essaie de combler ce manque en créant un agrégateur de flux rapide, facile à utiliser et à installer pour GTK/Gnome.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">‏Liferea הינו קיצור של Linux Feed Reader (קורא ערוצים של Linux). זהו מאגד חדשות עבור ערוצי חדשות מקוונים. זה תומך במספר של פורמטים שונים של ערוצים כולל RSS/RDF, ‏CDF וגם Atom. קיימים קוראי חדשות רבים אחרים זמינים, אך אלו לא זמינים עבור Linux או מצריכים ספריות חיצוניות רבות על מנת שיותקנו. Liferea מנסה לגשר על פער זה על ידי יצירת מאגד חדשות עבור GTK/GNOME מהיר, קל לשימוש, קל להתקנה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Liferea ialah akronim untuk Linux Feed Reader. Agregator berita untuk feed berita online. Mendukung berbagai format feed yang berbeda termasuk RSS/RDF, CDF dan Atom. Ada banyak pembaca berita yang tersedia, namun tidak tersedia untuk Linux atau memerlukan pustaka ekstra untuk diinstal. Liferea mencoba untuk memenuhinya dengan membuat agregator untuk GTK/GNOME yang cepat, mudah digunakan, mudah diinstall.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Liferea është një shkurtim për Linux Feed Reader. Është një grumbullues lajmesh për prurje lajmesh në internet. Mbulon një numër formatesh prurjeje, përfshi RSS/RDF, CDF dhe Atom. Ka mjaft lexues të tjerë lajmesh, por këta nuk gjenden për Linux-in ose lypin shumë librari ekstra, pa të instalohen. Liferea orvatet ta plotësojë këtë mungesë duke krijuar një grumbullues lajmesh për GTK/GNOME, të shpejtë, të lehtë për t’u instaluar dhe përdorur.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Liferea är en förkortning av Linux Feed Reader. Det är en nyhetsläsare för nyhetsflöden på nätet. Det stödjer ett antal olika flödesformat inklusive RSS/RDF, CDF och Atom. Det finns många andra nyhetsläsare tillgängliga, men dessa andra finns inte tillgängliga för Linux eller kräver många extra bibliotek för installation. Liferea försöker att fylla detta tomrum genom att skapa en snabb, lättanvänd, lätt installerbar nyhetsläsare för GTK/GNOME.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Liferea, Linux Feed Reader'ın bir kısaltmasıdır. Çevrim içi haber beslemeleri için bir haber toplayıcısıdır. RSS/RDF, CDF ve Atom gibi çok sayıda farklı besleme biçimini destekler. Birçok haber okuyucu bulunabilir fakat bunlar Linux'ta kullanılamayabilir ya da yüklenmek için birçok ek kütüphane gereksinir. Liferea; hızlı, kullanımı kolay, GTK/GNOME için kurulumu kolay haber toplayıcısı olarak bu boşluğu kapatmayı denemektedir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Liferea là từ viết tắt từ Linux Feed Reader. Nó là một bộ tập hợp tin tức cho các feed tin tức trực tuyến. Nó hỗ trợ một lượng lớn các định dạng feed khác nhau bao gồm RSS/RDF, CDF và Atom. Hiện sẵn có nhiều bộ đọc tin tức, nhưng những cái khác đó không sẵn có trên Linux hay yêu cầu cài đặt bổ sung nhiều thư viện. Liferea có để lấp đầy khoảng trống này bằng các tạo cho môi trường  GTK/GNOME một bộ tập hợp tin tức nhanh, dễ cài đặt và sử dụng.</p>
    <p>Distinguishing features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funcionalidades distintivas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">תכונות מיוחדות:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur istimewa:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità distintive:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">特徴的な機能:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sq">Veçori Për T’u Përmendur</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Mükemmel özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Визначні особливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Các tính năng phân biệt:</p>
    <ul>
     <li>Read articles when offline</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Lectura de artículos sin conexión</li>
     <li xml:lang="fi">Lue artikkeleita kun et ole yhteydessä verkkoon</li>
     <li xml:lang="fr">Lire les articles hors-ligne</li>
     <li xml:lang="id">Baca artikel ketika luring</li>
     <li xml:lang="sq">Lexoni artikujt kur jeni i palidhur</li>
     <li xml:lang="tr">Çevrim dışı iken maddeleri oku</li>
     <li xml:lang="uk">Читання статей у автономному режимі.</li>
     <li xml:lang="vi">Đọc các bài viết khi ngoại tuyến</li>
     <li>Synchronizes with TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="ar">المزامنة مع قارئ TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="de">Synchronisiert mit TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Sincronización con TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="fi">Synkronoi TheOldReaderin kanssa</li>
     <li xml:lang="he">סנכרון בעזרת TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="id">Sinkronisasi dengan TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="it">Sincronizza con TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="ja">TheOldReader との同期</li>
     <li xml:lang="ru">Синхронизация с TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="sq">Njëkohësohet me TheOldReader-in</li>
     <li xml:lang="sv">Synkroniserar med TheOldReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="uk">Синхронізація з TheOldReader.</li>
     <li xml:lang="vi">Đồng bộ hóa với TheOldReader</li>
     <li>Synchronizes with TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="ar">المزامنة مع TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Sincronización con TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="fi">Synkronoi TinyTinyRSS:n kanssa</li>
     <li xml:lang="fr">Synchroniser avec TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="he">סנכרון בעזרת TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="it">Sincronizza con TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="ja">TinyTinyRSS との同期</li>
     <li xml:lang="ru">Синхронизация с TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="sq">Njëkohësohet me TinyTinyRSS-në</li>
     <li xml:lang="sv">Synkroniserar med TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li xml:lang="tr">TinyTinyRSS ile eşzamanlar</li>
     <li xml:lang="uk">Синхронізація з TinyTinyRSS.</li>
     <li xml:lang="vi">Đồng bộ hóa với TinyTinyRSS</li>
     <li>Synchronizes with InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="ar">المزامنة مع قارئ InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="de">Synchronisiert mit InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Sincronización con InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="fi">Synkronoi InoReaderin kanssa</li>
     <li xml:lang="fr">Synchroniser avec les InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="he">סנכרון בעזרת InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="it">Sincronizza con InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="sq">Njëkohësohet me InoReader-in</li>
     <li xml:lang="sv">Synkroniserar med InoReader</li>
     <li xml:lang="tr">InoReader ile eşzamanlar</li>
     <li xml:lang="uk">Синхронізація з InoReader.</li>
     <li>Synchronizes with Reedah</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Sincronización con Reedah</li>
     <li xml:lang="fi">Synkronoi Reedahin kanssa</li>
     <li xml:lang="fr">Synchroniser avec Reedah</li>
     <li xml:lang="he">סנכרון בעזרת Reedah</li>
     <li xml:lang="it">Sincronizza con Reedah</li>
     <li xml:lang="ja">Reedah との同期</li>
     <li xml:lang="sv">Synkroniserar med Reedah</li>
     <li xml:lang="tr">Reedah ile eşzamanlar</li>
     <li xml:lang="uk">Синхронізація з Reedah.</li>
     <li>Permanently save headlines in news bins</li>
     <li xml:lang="ar">حفظ عناوين الأخبار بشكل دائم في سلة الأخبار</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Guardado permanente de titulares en bandejas de noticias</li>
     <li xml:lang="fr">Sauvegarder des titres dans des boîtes à nouvelles</li>
     <li xml:lang="he">אחסון כותרות באופן קבוע בתוך סלי איסוף</li>
     <li xml:lang="id">Simpan headline di news bin</li>
     <li xml:lang="it">Salve permanentemente le testate nell'archivio notizie</li>
     <li xml:lang="ru">Постоянное хранение заголовков в ящиках новостей</li>
     <li xml:lang="sq">Ruaji përgjithmonë titujt në kosha lajmesh</li>
     <li xml:lang="sv">Spara permanent rubriker i nyhetslådor</li>
     <li xml:lang="tr">Haber başlıklarını haber sepetlerinde kalıcı olarak sakla</li>
     <li xml:lang="uk">Зберігання заголовків записів новин.</li>
     <li xml:lang="vi">Lưu vĩnh viễn tin chính vào một bin tin tức</li>
     <li>Match items using search folders</li>
     <li xml:lang="ar">تجميع العناصر باستخدام مجلدات البحث</li>
     <li xml:lang="de">Filtern von Schlagzeilen mit Suchordnern</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Correspondencia de artículos mediante carpetas virtuales</li>
     <li xml:lang="fi">Hae tuloksia käyttämällä hakukansioita</li>
     <li xml:lang="fr">Retrouvez des articles en utilisant des dossiers de recherche</li>
     <li xml:lang="he">התאמת פריטים באמצעות תיקיות חיפוש</li>
     <li xml:lang="id">Item yang sesuai menggunakan pencarian folder</li>
     <li xml:lang="it">Abbina gli articoli usando le cartelle di ricerca</li>
     <li xml:lang="ru">Объединение новостей в папках поиска</li>
     <li xml:lang="sq">Gjej përputhje për zëra duke përdorur dosje kërkimi</li>
     <li xml:lang="sv">Matcha artiklar med hjälp av sökmappar</li>
     <li>Play Podcasts</li>
     <li xml:lang="de">Podcasts abspielen</li>
     <li xml:lang="es">Reproducción de podcasts</li>
     <li xml:lang="fi">Toista podcasteja</li>
     <li xml:lang="fr">Lire les Podcast</li>
     <li xml:lang="he">ניגון פודקסטים</li>
     <li xml:lang="id">Mainkan Podcast</li>
     <li xml:lang="it">Riproduce i podcast</li>
     <li xml:lang="ja">Podcastを演奏する</li>
     <li xml:lang="ru">Воспроизведение подкастов</li>
     <li xml:lang="sq">Luaj Podcast-e</li>
     <li xml:lang="sv">Spela poddsändningar</li>
     <li xml:lang="tr">Podcastleri Oynat</li>
     <li xml:lang="vi">Chơi Podcast</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="837" height="657">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot1.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="833" height="656">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot2.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="837" height="657">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot3.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="837" height="657">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot4.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="837" height="657">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot5.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="837" height="657">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot6.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="642" height="438">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot7.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="834" height="657">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot8.png</image></screenshot>
    <screenshot type="default"><image width="837" height="657">https://lzone.de/liferea/screenshots/screenshot9.png</image></screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://lzone.de/liferea/</url>
  <update_contact>liferea-devel@lists.sf.net</update_contact>
</component>